Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-1990-096
  - WAF/CP and Hub - Donors and Resources, Series 5
    - Hub Hank Harris (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Julia Hirsch (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Hunt, Helen (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hub - Inc. Magazine (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1984 - Inequality WAF/CP of Sacrifice (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - International Exposition of Rural Development 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Jenny Article - Wash. Post 6/19/83 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP JPTA (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Johnson Foundation (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Susan S. Keane Foundation (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hub Kristina Kiehl (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hub Michael Kieschnick (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hub AETNA (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hub Atlantic Richfield Foundation (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hub CIGNA (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hub Conn. Nat'l Bank - Maxine Deane (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - EDA Economic Development Admin. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Ensworth Charitable Trust (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Hub Ford Foundation (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Fund for New Jersey (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Hearst FDN '84 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - HHS Health and Human Services (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Hub Conrad H. Hilton FDN. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Joint FDN Support (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Hub Levi - Strauss FDN. Enterprise FDN. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - C.S. Mott FDN. Geraldine Larkin (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Hub N.W. Area FDN. St. Paul Judith Healey (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Jessie Smith Noyes FDN. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Phoenix Mutual - Hartford (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Hub: Prudential Alex Plinio (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Hub Funding - Ann Roberts (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Hub Funding - Rockefeller Family Fund (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hub Sherwood Forest Fund (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Hub Traveler's (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Victoria Foundation, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Hub LISC South Bronx Tour (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Lewis, Howard and Jane (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Lucia Woods Lindley (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Kate Rand Lloyd (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Luce Foundation (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Mally Foundation Dr. John Brewer (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Etzweiler, Marion: Minn. Fdn. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP M.A.L.D.E.F. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hub Jewel Jackson McCabe (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP "Making Competition Work For Us" (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Mary McDermott (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hub - Jack Meyer (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Midwest Women's Center - Chicago (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hub - David Morris (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Charles Stewart Mott Foundation (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Ms. Foundation - Joyce Yu (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Ms. Foundation "Women's Funding Assist. Project" (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP - Steven Minter (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP NAACP LDF - Fairfax Proposal (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Hub - National Assoc. of Bank Women (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - WAF/CP Nat'l Assoc. of Bank Women (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP: National Committee on Responsive Philanthropy (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Hub Nat'l Congress for Comm. Econ. Development (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - WAF/CP National Networks (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Hub National Museum of Women's Art (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - WAF/CP National Network of Grantmakers (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - WAF/CP Nat'l Urban League (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - WAF/CP New Federation Impact (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - WAF/CP N.Y. Community Trust (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Hub - N.Y. Partnership Peggy Dulaney (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Partnership's Exchange - Alice Shabecoff (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - WAF/CP New York Refs. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Eleanor Holmes Norton Hub (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Hub Nuclear Disarmament (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP John Olsen (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Oppenstein Brothers Foundation (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Overseas Education Fund (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP PIPR (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Packard Foundation (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Bob Payton (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Peninsula Community Foundation (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Pres.'s Advisory Committee for Women (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Potlatch Corporation (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Private Philanthropy (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Project on the Status and Education of Women (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Public Policy Action (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Quitman, Yolanda (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Rockefeller - Single Heads of Household (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Hub WAF/CP Barbara Rose - Alaska Consulting Group (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - RWL Speeches (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Rubin, Nancy Miles (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP San Mateo FDN (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - WAF/CP Skid Row Develop. Corp - Martha Braun Hicks (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Jane Skinner (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Hub - South Shore Bank (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Wiseman, Kathleen (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Hub Stanford Entrepreneurship (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Stanford Med-Peninsula Urban Coalition (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Suzanne Strickland (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP SRI International (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1983 Clippings - Women (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1981-82 Clippings on Women (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Advocates for Women (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP A.F.S. Comm. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hub - Appalshop (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Awed (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Big Sisters: D. Hill and M. Branch (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Hub Center for Women in Government (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP CWSS (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Coal Employment Project (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP "Meets the Computer Age (Computer Workshop) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP CROW-TECH Asst. - Center for Research on Women (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP: Civic Center and Clearinghouse: Herta Loeser (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Crittenton Friends (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Community Foundation of New Jersey (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Denver - Better Jobs for Women - Apprenticeships (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Equal Rights Advocates - Nancy Davis (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Equity Institute (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP General Technical Assistance 1981-82 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Tech. Asst. Mtg. July 29, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP General Technical Assistance 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Girls Clubs (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Gold Rush Women (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Girl Scouts of U.S.A. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Jazzmobile (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP: MODY - LDC Women in Development - Communication Careers (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP LKL Productions (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Los Angeles Committee on Assaults Against Women (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP MELD (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Mid-Peninsula Support Network for Battered Women (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Midwest Women's Center (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Mississippi (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - NARAL Foundation (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP National Commission on Working Women (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP National Congress of Neighborhood Women (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Institute for Comprehensive Understanding (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hub - Nat'l Inst. for Women of Color (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hub - Nat'l Info. and Training Center - Gale Cincotta (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hub - Nat'l Urban Coalition - Alice Shakecoff (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Nat'l Women's Education Fund (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Hub National Women's Health Network (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP National Women's Law Center (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - WAF/CP Development Folders, Series 6
    - WAF/CP 1980 Submission Statement (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP 1979 Submission Statement (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP 8/27/79 Submission Statement (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP: 1978-79 Fund Raising/Funding Proposal (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Abelard Foundation (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Aetna (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Allied Chem. Corp: Morristown, N.J. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Amerada Hess Corp. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP American Express/Fireman's Fund (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP ARCA Foundation (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Astor Foundation - Linda Gilles (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Atlantic Richfield (ARCO) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Avon Products Foundation, New York (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Mary Reynolds Babcock Fdn. - Bill Bondurant (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Bank of America (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Bechtel Corp. - George Shultz (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Benson and Associates (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP Blandin Foundation (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Blaugrund Foundation (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - WAF/CP Boise Cascade (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP Borden Fdn., Colombus (J. Barker) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - WAF/CP Borg-Warner Fdn Margo Dunlap (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - WAF/CP Boston Safe Deposit and Trust Co. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - WAF/CP Otto Bremer Foundation (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bristol Meyers Fund, New York (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - WAF/CP Florence V. Burden Fdn. N.Y. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - WAF/CP Bush Foundation (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - WAF/CP Business and Professional Women's Foundation (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - WAF/CP Butler Family Fdn. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - WAF/CP The Cargill Foundation (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - WAF/CP Carnegie Corporation, New York (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - WAF/CP CBS Foundation (Helen Brown) (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - WAF/CP Chemical Bank (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - WAF/CP Chevron (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - WAF/CP Chicago Community Trust (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - WAF/CP Chicago Tribune (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Edna McConnell Clark; Patricia Carry Stewart (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Robert Sterling Clark Fdn., N.Y. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Cleveland Foundation (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Columbia/Fleishacker Fdns. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Commonwealth Fund - Margaret Malhoney (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Coors Foundation -Linda Tofaya (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Cummins Engine Fdn., Columbus (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Dallas Comm. Chest Trust Fund (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Dayton Hudson Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP William H. Donner Foundation (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Duke Endowment (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Equitable Life Assurance Society (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP ESMARK Foundation (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Exxon Corporation, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Maurice Falk Medical Fund (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Samuel S. Fels Fund (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP First National Bank of Boston (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Fisher Charitable Trust (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - WAF/CP Ford Foundation (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP General Mills Foundation (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - WAF/CP Gerbode Foundation (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - WAF/CP Glenmede Trust Co., aka Pew Memorial Trust and Wister (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - WAF/CP William T. Grant Foundation (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - WAF/CP Gries Charity Fund (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - WAF/CP Gries Financial Services (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - WAF/CP George Gund Fdn., Cleveland (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - WAF/CP Paul and Mary HAAS Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - WAF/CP Walter and Evelyn Haas Fund (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - WAF/CP Hancock Foundation (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Harris Bank - Chicago Mary Acker (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - WAF/CP Hawaiian Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - WAF/CP The Edward W. Hazen Foundation (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - WAF/CP Hearst Foundation (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - WAF/CP - Submission Hewlett Fdn. - Roger Heyns (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - WAF/CP Hewlett Packard (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - WAF/CP Hogg Foundation (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - WAF/CP IBM (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - WAF/CP Individual Contributions (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - WAF/CP International Paper Co., N.Y. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Irvine Foundation (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - WAF/CP Irwin/Sweeney/Miller/ Fdn., N.Y. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - WAF/CP Jerome Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - WAF/CP Robert Wood Johnson Foundation (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - WAF/CP The Joyce Foundation (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - WAF/CP Submission Kaiser Family Fdn. - Robert Glaser (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - WAF/CP Greater Kansas City Comm. Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - WAF/CP J.M. Kaplan Fund (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - WAF/CP W.K. Kellog Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - WAF/CP Kern Foundation (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Albert Kundstadter Family Foundation (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Levi-Strauss (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Lilly Endowment, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Lucia Woods Lindley (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Joe and Emily Lowe Foundation (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP MacArthur Foundation (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP 3M Corporation (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP McGraw-Hill (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP The McIntosh Foundation (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP McKnight Foundation (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Bette Claire McMurray Foundation (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Montgomery Ward Fdn. - Denise Davis (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Moody Foundation (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Motorola Foundation (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Charles Stewart Mott Foundation (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Stewart R. Mott (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP Ms. Foundation (Rochelle Korman) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Joint Foundation Support (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Needmor Fdn., Toledo, Oh. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP New World Fdn. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - WAF/CP New York Fdn., NY (Madeline Lee) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - WAF/CP N.Y. Life Insurance Co. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - WAF/CP New York Times Fdn. - Fred Hechinger (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - WAF/CP Norman Foundation, Inc., N.Y. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - WAF/CP Northwest Area Foundation (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - WAF/CP Packard Foundation (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - WAF/CP Penn Mutual (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - WAF/CP William Penn Fdn. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - WAF/CP J.C. Penny Co., Inc. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - WAF/CP Pew Charitable Trust (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - WAF/CP Philip Morris, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - WAF/CP Pillsbury Company (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - WAF/CP Piton Foundation (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - WAF/CP: Pittsburgh Bridge and Iron Works Charitable Trust (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - WAF/CP Playboy Foundation (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - WAF/CP Polaroid Foundation (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - WAF/CP Potlatch Corporation (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - WAF/CP Powell Family Fdn. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - WAF/CP Prudential Foundation (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - WAF/CP Raychem Corporation (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - WAF/CP Charles H. Revson Foundation, NY (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - WAF/CP Sid Richardson Fdn. - Valleau Wilkie (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - WAF/CP - Ann R. Roberts (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - WAF/CP Rockefeller Family Fund (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - WAF/CP Rockefeller Foundation (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - WAF/CP: Rosenburg Foundation (Kirke Wilson: (55)421-6105) (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - WAF/CP Helena Rubinstein Foundation, NY (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - WAF/CP Russell Sage Foundation Marshall Robinson (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - WAF/CP Safeco Ins. Co of America - Mary Malarkey (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - WAF/CP San Francisco Foundation (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - WAF/CP Sears Roebuck Fdn. - Sarah Hargrave (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - WAF/CP Seattle - First National Bank (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - WAF/CP St. Paul Companies, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - WAF/CP St. Paul Foundation (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Stanford Oil Co. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Stulsaft Foundation (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Hattie M. Strong Fdn. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Syntex Corporation (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Taconic Foundation (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Time-Life Incorporated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Times Mirror Co. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Trull Foundation (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Unio Carbide Corp. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP United California Bank (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Villers Foundation (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Vincent Astor Fdn. - Linda Gilles (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Wenner - Gren Foundation (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Westinghouse Electric Fund - Cecile Springer (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Weyerhaeuser Company Foundation (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Wiebolt Foundation, Chicago (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP The Window Fund (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP John Hay Whitney Foundation (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - WAF/CP Zellerbach Family Fund (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - WAF/CP Resource Files, Series 7
    - ESL'S Enterprise (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Billie Achilles (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Alison Baker (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bancel, Diane E. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Hub Micki Barnes (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Joy L. Beaton (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Jill K. Berman - Communi- Speak Incorporated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Eula Bingham (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Corinne Black Corporate Contributions (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Margaret Booth (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Boyer, Kay (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Stephanie Brown (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Buchanan, Constance (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Libby A. Cater (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Robert Choate (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Martha Church Hood College (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cirillo, Marie (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP Lisa Cobbs (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Joan Connor (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Carol Conroy (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP Alan B. Cooper (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Cullen, Diane (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Hub - Dianne Danley Mace (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - WAF/CP Margot Davis (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hub - Barbadlee Diamonstein (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - WAF/CP Christine Donovan (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - WAF/CP Patricia R. Duignan (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - WAF/CP Lauren Dunbar (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - WAF/CP Joan Dunlop (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - WAF/CP Brian Dyack (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Hub - Rona Feit (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - WAF/CP Mary Garvin (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - WAF/CP Prof. Carol Gilligan (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - WAF/CP Joan Goodin (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Hub Anita Gottlieb (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - WAF/CP Carol Guyer (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Harlow, Hattie Dorsey (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Hayden, Trudy (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - WAF/CP Janet Gray Hayes (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Hub - Lori Henry (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Sue Herzog (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Mary Ellen Hilliard (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Michael Holubar (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Florence Howe (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hub Inez Kaiiser &p Assoc. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Molly Keating: Questions (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Kilcullen, Michael (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Joanne M. Kliesonas (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Helen Kremholtz (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Sandra Kuntz (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Iuo Joan Lederer (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Diane Levine (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Marilyn Levy (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Mary Lindsay (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Iris F. Litt (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Mavis Lockwood (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - McCoy, Brown (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Millie McCoy (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Hub Jain Malkin (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP Victoria Maxwell (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - WAF/CP Catherine Menninger (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Hub Mary Mountcastle (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - WAF/CP Barbara Mulville U. Mass Boston (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - WAF/CP Rosalind Newman and Dancers (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - WAF/CP John Niggenmeyer (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - WAF/CP Pattie Nolan (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - WAF/CP Helen O'Bannon (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Hub - Wenda B. O'Reilly (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Hub - Janice Perlman NYC Partnership, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Hub - Thomas Peters (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - WAF/CP Barbara Ashley Phillips (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Joanne Pratt (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP: Donee Technical Assistance - Luisa Priddy (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Anne Ramsay (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Reed, Ingrid (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Reynolds, Jennifer (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Elton Richardson (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Hub - Fran Roelfsema (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Joyce Ream and Anne Hoblitzelle (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Rooks, Judith and Charles (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Sandra Rosenblith LISC (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Dr. Allen Rosenfeld (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - WAF/CP Mary Rowe (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Heidi Schmidt - Colo. Open Space Council (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Marsorie Hansen Shaevitz (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Donna Shalala (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Eleanor Shelling (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP Rebecca Sive-Tomashefsky - Playboy Foundation (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Jenny Smith; Melissa Smith (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Soto, Dalka (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - WAF/CP Peggy Stern (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Hub - Karl Stauber (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - WAF/CP Peg Stone (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - WAF/CP Susie Suafai (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - WAF/CP Irene Tinker EPOC (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Toole, Barbara B. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Reva Tooley 356 S. Rossmore Ave. L.A., CA 90020 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Hub Vicki Warner (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Florence Weicker (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Gardenia White (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Pat Woolf (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Wooten, Wanda (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Charlotte Wyman (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hub Employment Welfare Enterprise Clipping File (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Back Files 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - WAF/CP - Fair housing, Series 8
    - Staff Reference Manual - The Cleveland Foundation - Greater Cleveland Associated Foundation (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Tarnished Golden Door - Civil Rights Issues in Immigration (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Teaching and Learning Research Grants Announcement - NIE (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Conference on the Educational and Occupational Needs of American Indian Women (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Teaching and Learning Research Grants Announcement - NIE (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Conference on the Educational Needs of Hispanic Women (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Conference on the Educational and Occupational Needs of White Ethnic Women (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Conference on the Educational and Occupational Needs of Black Women vol. 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Grants for Research on Desegregation (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - [loose binder] Fair Housing - Fair Lending Legal Seminar for Attorneys and Officials of Lending Institutions (Box 3)
  - WAF/CP International, Series 9
    - Board Meeting Nov. 16, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Annual Mtg. Detroit April 27-28, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Board Feb. 2-3, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Ad Hoc Corporate Cdm. 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Development - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP 1982 Development (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Internal Organization 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Membership Com. 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Membership Div. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Publications (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP United Nations Decade for Women (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Urban Institute (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Welcome to the Club" (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Challenging Discriminate in Private Clubs (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hub Women's Bureau Depart. of Labor (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hub Timothy Wirth (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Hub Joan Wills Nat'l Gov's Assoc. CfED Paper (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP The Women's Foundation (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Women's Foundation (Box 3, Folder 1)